JONATHAN HEBERT

Full Stack - Front End Developer

Riverdale, MI 48877 fullstack926@gmail.com 14044925275

I am a passionate software engineer who started programming in grade school. After getting bachelor's degree in computer science, I worked for two large international companies- developing mostly web applications for several years. I am accustomed to a distributed environment and working with remote clients using agile methodologies

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

Avatar Engines LLC

December 2019 to Present

Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/In versify and MongoDB.

Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node.js, and Mongoose.

Implemented complex UI components with React/Type Script and SCSS.

Wrote scripts to use and manipulate data from various sources.

Expert Front-end Developer

Thinkover

January 2017 to November 2019

Designed the application architecture.

Led the front-end development.

Implemented a mobile-first responsive design.

Introduced Sass style guides for a responsive design.

Improved the overall user experience.

React Developer

Zuehlke Engineering

September 2015 to November 2016

Migrated an AngularJS codebase into React.

Developed a prototype used to visualize transportation routes using React, Antd, and Deck.gl.

Implemented new features on community platform.

Improved the front-end architecture by reorganizing modules.

Composed scripts-with Python and Node.js-to parse complex data structures.

Software Developer

Levi9 Global Sourcing Balkan June 2014 to August 2015

Worked as a part of an agile team in the development of an enterprise service bus for

Amsterdam Airport.

Designed and developed multiple OSGI modules for integration with external and internal systems. Redesigned and refactored a system making it more maintainable and highly testable. Introduced guidelines for unit testing on a project.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

University of Toronto - Toronto, ON 2011 to 2014

Skills

- Git
- Bootstrap
- AJAX
- Java
- JSON
- Unit Testing
- SOAP
- SQL
- User Interface (UI)
- JavaScript
- React
- PHP
- TypeScript
- CSS
- jQuery
- Laravel
- Angular
- HTML5
- Express.js
- Node.js
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Vue.js
- Next.js
- MongoDB
- REST
- GitHub
- AWS

- MVC
- APIs

Languages

• English - Fluent

Links

https://portfolio-hebert.herokuapp.com